[{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678929492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":6220,"timeElapsed":31237},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678934398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4903,"timeElapsed":36143},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678937314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2912,"timeElapsed":39058},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678940094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2778,"timeElapsed":41839},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678943470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3372,"timeElapsed":45215},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678947368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3895,"timeElapsed":49113},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678950492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3120,"timeElapsed":52237},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678953736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3241,"timeElapsed":55481},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678955935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2196,"timeElapsed":57680},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678964105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":6372,"timeElapsed":65850},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678968341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4232,"timeElapsed":70086},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678971136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2792,"timeElapsed":72881},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678973352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2213,"timeElapsed":75097},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678976301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2947,"timeElapsed":78046},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678979705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3401,"timeElapsed":81450},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678982907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3199,"timeElapsed":84652},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678985184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2275,"timeElapsed":86929},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678987402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2215,"timeElapsed":89147},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678994116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5473,"timeElapsed":95861},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678996355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2236,"timeElapsed":98100},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678998779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2422,"timeElapsed":100524},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679000901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2119,"timeElapsed":102646},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679003295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":105040},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679005615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2318,"timeElapsed":107360},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679008422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2804,"timeElapsed":110167},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679010508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2084,"timeElapsed":112253},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679012618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2107,"timeElapsed":114363},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679019617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":5375,"timeElapsed":121362},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679022105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2484,"timeElapsed":123850},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679024492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2384,"timeElapsed":126236},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679031881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7388,"timeElapsed":133626},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679034028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2144,"timeElapsed":135773},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679036424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2394,"timeElapsed":138169},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679038888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2461,"timeElapsed":140633},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679041396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2506,"timeElapsed":143141},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679043229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1830,"timeElapsed":144974},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679048029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3615,"timeElapsed":149774},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679051259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3228,"timeElapsed":153004},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679054667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3405,"timeElapsed":156412},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679056632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1962,"timeElapsed":158377},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679058586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1952,"timeElapsed":160331},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679060470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1881,"timeElapsed":162215},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679062167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1695,"timeElapsed":163912},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679064469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2300,"timeElapsed":166214},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2377,"timeElapsed":168594},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679074055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":6136,"timeElapsed":175800},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679080398,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6340,"timeElapsed":182143},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679083107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2706,"timeElapsed":184852},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679084936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1827,"timeElapsed":186681},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679086832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1893,"timeElapsed":188577},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679088707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1872,"timeElapsed":190452},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2267,"timeElapsed":192722},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679093305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2327,"timeElapsed":195050},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679095062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1754,"timeElapsed":196807},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679096665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1599,"timeElapsed":198409},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679104729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6365,"timeElapsed":206474},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679106514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1782,"timeElapsed":208259},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679108881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2364,"timeElapsed":210626},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679110964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2079,"timeElapsed":212709},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679113443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2477,"timeElapsed":215188},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679115239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1794,"timeElapsed":216984},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679117776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2534,"timeElapsed":219521},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679119748,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1970,"timeElapsed":221493},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679121833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2083,"timeElapsed":223578},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679127620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3928,"timeElapsed":229365},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679130616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2994,"timeElapsed":232361},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679133406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2787,"timeElapsed":235151},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679138150,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4741,"timeElapsed":239895},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679140646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2494,"timeElapsed":242391},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679142895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2247,"timeElapsed":244640},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679145227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":246972},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679147379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2149,"timeElapsed":249123},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679149378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1996,"timeElapsed":251123},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679151069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1688,"timeElapsed":252813},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679157556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":5473,"timeElapsed":259301},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679159421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":1862,"timeElapsed":261166},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679161288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1864,"timeElapsed":263033},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679163379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2088,"timeElapsed":265124},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679165651,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2270,"timeElapsed":267396},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679171052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5399,"timeElapsed":272797},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679173867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2813,"timeElapsed":275612},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3279,"timeElapsed":278894},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679178874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1722,"timeElapsed":280618},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679184324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4248,"timeElapsed":286069},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679186498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2171,"timeElapsed":288243},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679188893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2393,"timeElapsed":290638},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679191286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2392,"timeElapsed":293031},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679193404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2115,"timeElapsed":295149},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679196138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2732,"timeElapsed":297883},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679198550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2410,"timeElapsed":300295},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679200692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2140,"timeElapsed":302437},{"subjectID":"8k0tyk0vu4","prolificID":"5ba292385301b80001c71ba2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b5ca6064173cd1040","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679202714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2019,"timeElapsed":304459}]